https://billericaylions.com/sandbox/privacy-policy-2/

Billericay Lions Club Privacy Policy
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)
Privacy Policy
Billericay Lions respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. It provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of its Privacy Policy and practices and of the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and how that information is used. We make this notice readily available on our home page and at the bottom of every web page on this site.
What information we collect from you
There are two types of information we collect: information that allows us to identify specific individuals and information of a more generalised nature.
Personal information
Whenever we ask for information that enables us to identify you it will be clear that we are doing so and in every case you will have a choice of how we use the information that is asked for. Information of this type will only be asked for on those parts of our web site that allows transactions to be performed, in contrast to those parts of our web site that are merely informational in their function.
Information of this type will also be collected when you contact us directly by email for any reason or if you specifically request that we send you information.
Anonymised information
This website uses cookies to help you in your interactions with the site. No personally identifiable data is collected. This type of information helps us to enhance the web site and improve its navigability. It also helps us to improve the quality of the online sector and information you can access. In order to facilitate this, we use cookies to identify specific information about your visits to the site.
This website is hosted by TSO Host using cPanel who provide standard metrics out of the box https://cpanel.com. Google Analytics www.google.com/intl/en_uk/analytics is also available but is currently not used. These allow us to track how popular our site is and to record visitor trends over time. Google Analytics uses a cookie to help track which pages are accessed. The cookie contains no personally identifiable information, but it does use your computer’s IP address to determine where in the world you are accessing the site from, and to track your page visits within the site.
From time to time, we may embed external content from third-party websites (e.g. Facebook, YouTube) within our website. These websites may utilise cookies and the Privacy Policy that will apply to such third-party content will be that published on the website of that third-party content provider.
Sites covered by this policy
This privacy Policy applies Billericay Lions owned websites https://www.billericaylions.com and http://billericaybeerfestival.billericaylions.com/
Links to non Billericay Lions websites
Both the Billericay Lions and Billericay Beer Festival websites may provide links to third party websites for your convenience and information. If you access those links, you will leave either of the Billericay Lions websites. Billericay Lions do not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from the Billericay Lions websites. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party websites. The Billericay Lions Privacy Policy does not cover the personal data that you choose to give to unrelated third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any organisation before submitting your personal information.
Children’s Privacy
Billericay Lions are committed to protecting the privacy needs of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.
Cookies
A “cookie” is a small data file transferred by a website to your computer hard drive. Accepting the cookies used on our site does not give us access to your personal information Cookies are typically classified as either “session” cookies or “permanent” cookies.
“Session” cookies do not stay on your computer after you leave our website or close your browser. The aggregate information collected permits us to analyse traffic patterns on our site. This can enable us over time to provide a better experience on our site by improving content or personalization and making our site easier to use.
“Permanent” cookies are those that remain on your computer. Billericay Lions do not utilise permanent cookies.
Most browsers automatically accept cookies by default, but you can usually refuse cookies or selectively accept certain cookies by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn off cookies, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you and some web pages may not display properly.
Changes to this Policy
If there are updates to the terms of Billericay Lions Online Privacy Policy, we will post those changes and update the revision date in this document, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have.
Contacting us
We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please email
Search for:
Search
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2015 – 2020 Billericay Lions
Facebook
Contact us
The Lions Club of Billericay is a Charitable Trust, our Registered Charity Number is 10008040.
Home
About Lions
Billericay Lions
International
Activities
Community Service
Charitable Donations
Investing in youth
Proudly powered by WordPress
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue browsing, we’ll assume that you are happy to receive all our cookies.OkPrivacy policy
